## Raymond Bello

Electrical Engineer

### Contact

Address
Ottawa, ON, K1S5M2

**Phone** 289 925 4702

**E-mail** raymondbello11@gmail.com

**WWW** raymondbello.github.io

#### **Skills**

Python

SystemVerilog

C/C++

**MATLAB** 

Real-time Embedded Systems

System-level electrical design and integration

Algorithm Design

Control System Performance Tuning

Knowledgeable in PCBA

Wiring schematics

Time management

Strong problem-solving skills

Code reviews

Team Building

Ambitious electrical engineer with a strong desire to apply education to root cause analysis in product development. Committed to successful project rollouts with ability to work with all types of personalities. Experience working with cutting-edge technologies and emerging concepts.

### **Work History**

2020-01 -2020-05

# ASIC Design and Verification Intern/Co-Op Engineer

Ciena Corp., Ottawa, Ontario

- Collaborated with design teams on design reviews and validation testing for RTL blocks and FEC components.
- Followed specifications and technical limitations when designing to meet established design objectives.
- Authored and verified detailed functional specifications for development.
- Developed test methodology to check software features and devised test plans for modules.
- Worked closely with ASIC/FPGA testing designers to execute and improve test coverage.

2018-04 -2018-09

#### **Technical Sales Associate**

Incredible Connection, Ottawa, Ontario

- Collaborated with customers and asked questions to assess needs and budgets.
- Recommended products and explained features and costs to help customers make educated buying decisions.
- Conducted on-site product demonstrations to highlight features, answer customer questions and redirect concerns toward positive aspects.
- Worked alongside retail representatives to boost sales by enhancing product presentations and advertising collateral.

### Education

2015-09 -Current

# Bachelor of Science: Electrical Engineering And Computer Technology

University Of Ottawa - Ottawa, Ontario

• Member of IEEE uOttawa

2013-08 -2015-04

### **High School Diploma**

Southern Ontario College - Hamilton, Ontario